name_list = ["henry", "praise", "achiri", "kate", "nehemiah", "kristal",
             "precious", "abena", "elijah", "kelvin", "stephen", "skekwonya",
             "stanley", "ergesis", "caleb"]

question_list = [
    {"question": "Which data type in python does not have the changeability characteristics:", "answer": "tuple"},
    {"question": "How do you open a file in Python:", "answer": "open()"},
    {"question": "Which data type in Python is unordered:", "answer": "dictionary"},
    {"question": "Which keyword function returns the number of items in an object, such as a string or list:", "answer": "len()"},
    {"question": "What keyword method in python is used to get the absolute value of a number:", "answer": "abs()"},
    {"question": "What is the result of the following?\n'hello silicon Accra Innovation School'.find('Innovation'):", "answer": "20"},
    {"question": "What is the result of the following?\n'hello silicon Accra Innovation School'.find('School'):", "answer": "31"},
    {"question": "What is the result of the following?\n'hello silicon Accra Innovation School'.find('ool'):", "answer": "34"},
    {"question": "How do you add element to a set in Python:", "answer": "set.add()"},
    {"question": "What is the keyword to join two sets in python:", "answer": "set.union()"}]
    
